结果可能不如我们所愿  盖瑞
The outcome was never in our favor, Gary.
有话直说吧  HUE
Cut it to me straight, HUE.
我有多大可能逃出这片混沌？
What are my chances of getting out of this mess?
以你现在的状态
In your current state,
再过10分钟  你就会死了
you will pass the point of recovery in 10 minutes.
你的氧气也在泄漏  盖瑞
You are also leaking O2, Gary.
哈  看哪  红色预警的界面竟然是绿色的
Huh, look at that. They went with green for a red alert.
要我弄  我肯定弄成红色的  或者蓝紫色
I mean, I would have went with red, a periwinkle.
喵的  蛋酒色也行
Heck, I mean, even egg nog.
我都不知道有没有这个颜色
I don't even know if that's a color,
不过  哦我的天哪  我现在好想喝蛋酒
but, oh, good Lord, now I just want egg nog.
根据泄漏速度  再过9分钟你就要死了
The rate of the leak will render you lifeless in nine minutes.
你真是好消息不断哪
You are really buttering me up with fantastic news.
根据我的预测  盖瑞
I'm afraid, Gary,
你恐怕无法幸存了
there is no foreseeable outcome where you survive.
这座位真是烂极了... 正好落在鼻血区了
These tickets suck ... right in the nosebleeds.
鼻血区（nosebleeds）：指大型演出里离舞台最远的区域，因为位置较高，被戏称“海拔高到流鼻血”。
鸭嘴兽字幕组出品
翻译 + 校对 + 压制：Kyl
Final Space - Episode One
终空  第一季第一集
Sync & Correction by f1nc0 from Addic7ed.com
本字幕仅供学习交流  请于下载后24小时内删除
托罗星云
463G区
啊！
Aah!
早上好  盖瑞  这是第1818天
Good morning, Gary. Day 1,818.
你能不能别这样？
How about freakin' no?
这次比往常更狠了  HUE！
That was a bit harder than normal, HUE!
你好啊  我亲爱的朋友
Hello, dear friend.
有段时间没见面了
It's been a while.
嘿！好极了！
Hey! Yes!
你怎么样  汉克？
What's up, Hank?
嗯  是的
Hmm, yeah.
贝丝今天看起来很漂亮  看看她
Beth is looking good today. Look at that.
用她魅力四射的大眼睛凝望着我
Staring at me with those hot eyes.
你  我... 一会见
You, me... later.
打牌吗  汉克？你想玩吗？
Cards, Hank? You want to play?
我需要找个人和我打牌
I need somebody to play with.
就决定是你了  啊！
So it's gonna be you. Aah!
我的牌都被你烧光了  汉克
I'm starting to run out of decks, Hank.
嘿  盖瑞！你好啊！
Hey, Gary! Hello!
哦  饼干  好极了！
Ooh, cookie, yummy!
哈！
Ha!
HUE？
HUE?
怎么了  盖瑞？
Yes, Gary?
我可以拿一块饼干吗？
Can I have a cookie?
嗯  不可以  盖瑞
Mm, no, Gary.
为啥不可以？你都给KVN打开了
Why not? You opened it for KVN.
那坨狗屎都不能吃饼干好嘛！
That sack of wet turds can't even eat cookies!
他只是把饼干怼进处理器槽里而已
He just smashes it into his processor slot.
我恨KVN... 非常恨他  他简直是我生命里的祸根
I hate KVN... so painfully. He's the blight of my life.
如果你拿了一块饼干
If you take a cookie,
我就不得不再给你加一天刑期了
I will be forced to add one full day to your sentence.
你觉得一天刑期  能吓倒一个舰长吗？
You think a full day scares the captain?
盖瑞  过去的五年里我每天都在和你解释
Gary, I've explained this to you every day for the past five years.
你不是舰长  你是这艘飞船上的囚犯
You are not the captain. You are a prisoner aboard this ship.
好像有那么一点点耳熟  现在  把柜门打开
Sounds vaguely familiar. Now, open this cabinet.
哦  它们真是太——好吃啦！
Oh, they're just so-o-o-o good!
嗯  嗯  嗯！
Mmm, mmm, mmm!
啊啊啊！
Aaaah!
你的刑期增加了一天
One day has been added to your sentence.
哦！我摸到了！舰长大人摸到了！
Oh! I touched one! The captain's touched one!
舰长日志80085
Captain's log 80085.
嗨  奎恩！猜猜是谁在找你！
Hey, Quinn! Guess who!
还是我  盖瑞  奎恩  我考虑好了
It's me, Gary, again. Quinn, I've thought on it,
我决定  鉴于今天是个大日子
and I've decided that since this is a big day,
是我们的纪念日  如你所知
the day of our anniversary, as you know,
是时候来点真的了
it's time to get real.
奎恩  这是... 这是真实又纯粹的盖瑞
Quinn, this ... this is the real raw Gary.
我过去一直没让你见到真实的盖瑞  现在我再也藏不下去了
It's been eating me up inside keeping the real raw Gary from you.
五年以来  你的存在一直
For five years, real raw Gary hasn't been able
在真实盖瑞的精神堡垒里挥之不去
to get you out of his mind fortress.
在我见到你的那天  我就知道你是我爱的人了
When I met you that day, I knew you were it.
把我们的东西还回来  盖瑞！
Give us what's ours, Gary!
讲真  这是我的！
Technically, it's mine!
- 布鲁斯特恩博士  还有德瑞克！   - 减减肥吧！
- Dr. Bluesteen and Derek! - Lose some weight!
地球
五年前
快点  德瑞克  跟紧！
Come on, Derek, keep up!
他们给了我一杯苏打水？
They gave me a seltzer?
为什么给我苏打水... 除非我点了一瓶
Why would they give me a seltzer... unless I ordered it.
我点了一瓶吗？是的  我点了！
Did I order it? Yes, I did!
我要把你的膝盖打碎  盖瑞！
I'm gonna break your knees, Gary!
我的老天爷啊
Sweet heavenly fire.
那个超级无敌性感的女士是谁？
Who is the muy bueno super spicy lady?
是奎恩·厄尔冈舰长  不过别想了
Captain Quinn Airgone. But don't bother.
如果你不是无疆守卫的人员  她可对你没兴趣
If you're not Infinity Guard, she's not interested.
实际上  我可是接近指挥链顶端的人呢
Actually, I'm pretty freaking high up in the command chain.
- 真的？   - 不骗你
- Really? - Yeah, really.
真的没骗我？
Seriously?
真的没骗你  我没法再贴近你的脸了
Seriously, I can't get any closer to your face, dude.
- 那你的制服在哪  老兄？   - 我有制服  老弟
- Then where's your uniform, bud? - I have one, guy.
- 你可没有  伙计   - 我有  朋友
- No, you don't, pal. - Yes, I do, chum!
我... 我落在厕所里了  狗带！
It's... in the bathroom. Crap!
呀！
Shwa!
看起来不错  盖瑞！
Looking good, Gary!
你要把他扔在这吗
You're just gonna leave him in there,
你个... 你个混蛋
you chuck ... you chuck-face!
哦  亲爱的阿司匹林
Oh, sweet aspirin.
三块钱  刚刚好！好极了！
Three dratnoids, exact change! Tight!
走你！
Swallow!
你是个好人  盖瑞！
You're a good guy, Gary.
天衣无... 呃！呃！
Now to be smooth as ... Uh! Uh!
这可是第一次  我连招呼都没打  就拿到了一个女孩的电话
First time I got a girl's number before I even said "Hey."
知道吗  我喜欢有很多电话号码的女孩
You see, I like that. I like a girl with a lot of phones.
实际上  这是普朗克常数
Actually, this is the solution to an internal inconsistency
内部不一致性的解  此前从来没人研究出来这个
in Planck's constant that's never been solved
因为至今都还没人发现这是个问题
because until now, no one realized it was a problem.
说到问题  我奉劝你现在就走
And speaking of problems, maybe you should leave
不然你也很成问题了... 你现在这样就已经很成问题了
before you become one ... as in now.
或者  我可以给你买杯喝的
Or I could buy you a drink.
- 真的？   - 让我们狂欢吧
- Really? - Let's get wild.
你给我买一杯如何？
How about you buy me a drink?
哇  不行  不过还是惊叹一下
Wow. I mean, no. But wow.
全体无疆守卫  立刻返回基地
All Infinity Guards, report back to base immediately.
- 咱们走！   - 去你家？
- Let's go! - Back to your place?
咱俩之间的进展简直和猎豹一样快  我喜欢这个
You're moving at cheetah speeds. I like it.
- 你还要去飞F71鹰式机呢  飞行员   - 哦我的天哪
- You have an F71 Hawk to fly, pilot. - Oh, my crap.
- 快起飞  飞行员！   - 你可以的  盖瑞
- Move this Hawk, pilot! - You can do this, Gary.
快学聪明点
Become a much smarter person now.
哦  双重狗带！
Oh, my double crap!
你不是飞行员吧？
You're not a pilot, are you?
- 我是啊...   - 吃我一拳！
- Yes, I am... - Punch!
我学到了深刻的教训
Lesson learned.
如果你真的想激怒整个政府
If you ever want to piss off a whole government,
就去轰掉92艘巡飞舰
just take out 92 star cruisers
外加一家家族经营的墨西哥餐馆
and a small family-owned Mexican restaurant.
对不起  瓜达露佩
Sorry, Guadalupe.
瓜达露佩（Guadalupe）：墨西哥一座著名天主教圣殿。
嘿！
Hyuh!
哇！
Wah!
你好啊盖瑞  我叫KVN
Hey, Gary. My name is KVN.
我是你的深空防精神错乱伴侣
I'm your deep space insanity avoidance companion.
- 很高兴见到你   - 我已经开始恨你了
- Nice to meet you. - I already hate you.
好消息是  再有一周
The good news is that I only have a week left
我就要从这个破烂的老鼠窝里离开了
to my sentence aboard this pathetic rat's nest.
发送！她这次一定会回复我的  HUE
And send! She's gonna respond this time, HUE.
有很大可能她不会回复你
There is a high probability she will not.
不过还是有一些可能她会回复我的  就是这样
But there's still a low probability she will. I'll take it!
完美搞定！
Nailed it!
你还有四个阵列要修
There are still four arrays that need to be repaired.
别烦我了  HUE
Get off my cheeks, HUE.
别烦我了  盖瑞
Get off my cheeks, Gary.
1891-C已经上线了
1891-C is back online.
HUE... 或许  现在还是周四？
HUE... by any chance, is it still Thursday?
过去的72个小时一直是周四
It's been Thursday for the last 72 hours.
好极了  那就还在播
Sweet. Then it's still on.
这一段是在恶搞《The Princess Bride》里的经典桥段。
我叫爱德华多·蒙托亚·塔拉金托·塔·拉卡拉·普利吉亚
My name is Eduardo Montoya Talakinto Ta Lacara Poligia.
你杀了我的父亲  现在  准备受死吧
You killed my father. Prepare to die.
盖瑞  你的休息时间结束了
Gary, your break is over.
但是杀死爱德华多·塔拉金托·塔拉·帕吉亚他爸的那个人
But the guy who killed Eduardo Talakinto Tala Pacia's father
还没准备受死呢！
hasn't prepared to die yet!
噫  那边有个... 有个逃跑的像素点
Dang, there's a ... there's a pixel on the loose.
-Whoo!
哦！
Oh!
有个外星人撞我脸上了！
It's an alien on my face!
有个外星人撞我... 还是个脸形的外星人！
It's an alien on my ... it's a face alien!
哦  你不是想吃我的脸  而是想抱我的脸啊
Oh. You're not a face-eater, you're a face-hugger.
Chookity.
我的生活需要一个抱我脸的东西
I need a face-hugger in my life.
Whoa!
你让我想起了我很久之前的一个朋友
You remind me of a friend I used to have a long time ago.
你觉得这个名字怎么样... “月饼”？
How do you like the name... Mooncake?
Whoa!
那就叫你月饼了
Mooncake it is.
我有点喘不上气了... 超激动
I'm pumped ... super-excited.
你不会碰巧还能说话吧  会吗？
You don't by chance speak real words, do you?
Chookity-pop.
哈！无所谓咯
Ha! Works for me.
泰拉·康·普莱姆
18650区
欢迎
Welcome.
你好小啊  天哪！什么... 哦！
You're so tiny, man! What ... oh!
听听别人怎么说你吧
Wait until the guys hear about this.
坐
Sit.
他在哪？！
Where is it?!
- 啥？！   - E-351
- What?! - E-351.
我... 我不知道
I ... I don't know.
我绝不对您撒谎  总司令
I would never lie to you, Lord Commander.
您知道的  只是... 我很抱歉  您个子真的太矮了！
You know, it's just ... I'm sorry, you're just so small!
这是... 这是... 哇！
It's ... it's... Wah!
你在哪找到它的？
Where did you find it?
不是我找到的它  是它找到我的
I didn't. It found me.
HUE对你知道的越少...
The less HUE ...
括号  在我们之间就把它当作混蛋就好  反括号
who, between us, is a bit of a dick like "whaaat?"
就越好
knows about you, the better.
好的  那就进去吧
Okay, let's get you in here.
准备好了吗？
You ready?
Chookity!
Chookity, Chookity!
求你了  合上啊
Please close.
好吧  大小不合适  不能用这个了
Okay, it's not fitting. It's not working.
Wow.
我有时会藏在这
I hide there sometimes.
就像个床垫小鬼
I'm like a mattress ghost.
要保密哦
Don't tell anyone.
Ooh.
哦  好极了！好... 不  一点也不好
Oh, perfect! Per... no, it's not perfect.
太糟糕了  为什么这么糟糕？！
That sucks. Why does that suck so hard?!
好吧  这样呢？
Okay, how about this?
有时我会藏... 我喜欢把
Sometimes I hide ... I like to hide from myself
自己的头藏在内裤里
by putting underwear on the circumference of my head.
这样如何？合适吗？
How about that? How's it fit?
Chookity.
好极了
Perfect.
求求你... 杀了我吧！
Please... just... kill... me!
想都别想  这样太粗鲁了
Wouldn't think of it. That would be rude.
吃
Eat.
HUE  发生了什么？
HUE, what is going on?
为什么飞船像静音的迪厅一样？
Why has the ship turned into a silent dance rave?
四艘不明飞船正在向我们的位置靠近
Four unknown vessels are descending upon our location.
从他们的标志来看  我认为
The markings lead me to believe
他们是来自文特里西的赏金猎人
they are Ventrexian bounty hunters.
让我激动一下  竟然有复杂生命体来了
Twist my nipples rough, we're talking complex life-forms.
棒极了！HUE  你一定要问清楚他们打不打牌
Yes! HUE, you must find out if they play cards.
我需要找人打牌！我需要  HUE！
I need this! I need this, HUE!
我... 我真的想和人打牌啊
I ... I really need somebody to play with.
启动安全协议
Activating security protocol.
HUE  什么鬼？！
HUE, what the crap?!
为了你的安全  你必须呆在大厅里
For your own safety, you must remain in the commissary.
为了我的安全？
For my own safety?
五年来我们第一次有访客上门  我还不能和他们玩玩？！
We get our first visitors in five years, and I can't mingle with them?!
HUE  马上开门！我想和他们玩！
HUE, open this door right now! I need to mingle!
我恐怕不能开门
I'm afraid I cannot.
你最好“恐怕”给我开个门！
You better afraid me up an open door!
- 哦  KVN来帮忙了！   - 我的老天哪  KVN！
- Ooh, let KVN help! - God almighty, KVN!
你能不能别这么神出鬼没的！
You can't just phantom up on me like that!
别担心嘛  我是来帮忙的
Don't worry about me, I am helping.
KVN  你终于办了一件正确的事
KVN, you did something right!
哦！
Ohh!
KVN  你这坨巨量电线球！
KVN, you processed horrendous mess of wires!
我们有权在你们的飞船上
Your vessel has been subjected
寻找E-351样本
to a search for specimen E-351.
快把它交出来  不然就等死吧
Come forward... or die.
哦我的天哪
Oh, crap.
我的胳膊  老天！啊啊啊！
My arm, man! Aaahh!
你个白痴！
You fool!
这他喵的是谁？
Who the freak is this guy?
我认为他们在找你书包里的那个外星人
I believe they want the alien you're hiding in your backpack.
什么？我不懂你在说啥
What? I don't know what you're referring to.
这才是我想做的事！我从没这么体验过活着的感觉！
This is what I was meant to do! I have never felt so alive!
哦！你说的是我的内裤小精灵
Oh! You mean my underpants caddy.
是的  我们最好服从他们的命令  盖瑞
Yes. We should comply with their wishes, Gary.
我不知道  我... 似乎开始喜欢上这个小家伙了
I don't know. I... kind of was starting to like this little guy.
他的拥抱很舒服
He gives great hugs.
盖瑞  我们的装备不足以应对这种威胁
Gary, we are not equipped to face this threat.
干得漂亮  阿瓦卡多
Good job, Avocato.
我们不能和他们打起来
This is not our fight.
HUE  我们就应该和他们打  你是无疆守卫啊
HUE, we make it our fight. You're Infinity Guard.
你的终极宗旨就是保护生命
Your whole motto is to protect life.
那是生命吗  盖瑞？
Is that life, Gary?
如果那都不算生命  那我就是一麻袋会发怒的核桃！
Well, if it isn't, then I'm a raging sack of walnuts!
HUE  启动光折！
HUE, lightfold the ship!
这将会延长你的刑期
This will lengthen your sentence.
我知道  启动光折  HUE！
I get it. Lightfold the ship, HUE!
盖瑞
Gary.
快啊！
Do it!
他们要光折了！
They're lightfolding!
接近警告  接近警告
Proximity alert. Proximity alert.
是我想的那样吗？
Is that what I think it is?
HUE  这可不妙  快带我们逃走！
HUE, that's no good. Get us out of here!
再光折一次！光折啊！
Lightfold again, lightfold, lightfold!
在光折引擎冷却之前  我们不能再动了
We are immobilized until the lightfold engines cool.
小行星群将在29秒后撞上飞船
The asteroids will reach the ship in 29 seconds.
立刻戴好头盔
Secure your helmet immediately.
我的头盔还在气闸里呢
My helmet's in the airlock.
快跑  还有15秒
Run. 15 seconds until impact.
以你现在的速度  你会赶不上的
At your current pace, you will not make it.
哦  盖瑞能赶上的
Oh, Gary will make it.
嘿  盖瑞  抱歉  你有空吗？
Hey, Gary, sorry, got a minute?
嗯  我在想...
Yeah, I've been thinking about...
呀！
Hyah!
盖瑞  两秒钟
Gary, two seconds.
要活下去啊！活下去啊！
You're gonna live! You're gonna live!
格兰多的手套啊！这次死翘了！
Sweet Grandor's glove! Definitely gonna die this time!
盖瑞  你可能会遇到麻烦
Gary, you may have a problem.
我严肃质疑你对“可能”一词的使用
I seriously question your usage of "may have".
我们“已经有”麻烦了  而且是很大的麻烦！
I think we have reached have. I am very deep in have!
由于卫星的引力
Due to the moon's gravity,
小行星带将会再次击中银河一号
the asteroid field will swing back to the Galaxy 1
然后在第39秒时击中你
and then at you in approximately 39 seconds.
这可不妙  HUE  给我出几个主意
That's no good, HUE. Formulate me up some solutions.
正在计算
Calculating. Mm-hmm.
嗯  嗯嗯
Mmm. Mnh-mnh.
啊  盖瑞  我想到一个方法
Ahh. Gary, I do have a solution
这个方法有33%的可能会成功
with a 33% chance of success.
好的  是什么方法？
Okay, and that would be?
从你的氧气罐里紧急喷射一次
Perform an emergency air blow-out of your O2 tanks.
如果你能进入卫星轨道
If you can enter the moon's orbit,
你就有可能沿着轨道转动  然后回到银河一号上
you might be able to sling-hook around it back to the Galaxy 1.
好的  好的  就这么办
All right. All right, let's do this.
盖瑞  你要知道  这个计算只对你一个人有效
Gary, you should know, this calculation will only work with you.
你需要把那个生命体丢掉
You will have to leave the life-form behind.
月饼？
Mooncake?
否则  你将完全没有可能
Or there is zero probability
活着回到银河一号上
you will make it back to the Galaxy 1 alive.
我明白了  然而我要证明你是错的  月饼会和我一起回去的
I get it. I'll scream at you. Mooncake is coming with.
你做不到的  盖瑞
You will never make it, Gary.
你唯一幸存的可能  就是独自进行这项行动
Your only chance is to perform this maneuver alone.
HUE  你太没信心了  真让人扫兴！
HUE, your lack of confidence is positively depressing!
喷气将在三秒后进行
Blowing the air tank in three...
盖瑞  拜托
Gary, please.
两秒...
Two...
你会失败的
You will fail.
你说对了  我会呈现一场光荣的失败
You're right. I will fail... upwards.
我会败进卫星轨道里
Entering into moon's orbit.
哦不！似乎不成
Oh, no! It's not working.
以你现在的速度
At your current rate of velocity,
你将无法回到银河一号了
you will not make it back to the Galaxy 1.
你失败了  盖瑞
You have failed, Gary.
小行星带将在五秒后击中你
The asteroids will make impact in five seconds.
四...
Four...
三...
Three...
二...
Two...
一
One.
成功了！
It worked!
HUE  你还说我会死的！哈！
HUE! And you said I could die! Ha!
你确实死过一次... 你死了五分钟
You were dead ... for five minutes.
你没骗我？
Are you for serious?
我认为  那个生命体救了你一命
I believe the life-form saved your life.
月饼？
Mooncake?
Chookity, Chookity.
谢谢你救了我
Thank you for saving my life.
Wow.
我依然监测到一个不明武装生命体在飞船上
I am detecting one unknown life-form still aboard. He is armed.
哪个船舱？
What deck?
4A  机器人已经在路上了
4A. SAMES are already on route.
把E-351交出来
Hand over E-351.
听着  伙计  我只问你一件事
Listen, buddy, I only have one thing to say to you.
你... 打牌吗？
Do you... play... cards?
我就当你打牌了！
I'm gonna take that as a yes!
- 不许动！   - 哦我的天哪！我的天
- Freeze! - Oh, good Lord! Oh, my gosh.
别这么蹦到别人面前好吗  汉克！
Just don't walk up on somebody like that, Hank!
你要把我吓尿了  我还以为你是小鬼呢
I'm gonna crap my pants. I thought you were a baby ghost
或者“鬼小弟”？总之是个小小的鬼之类的
or a ghost baby or something in between the ghost baby spectrum.
不许动！
Freeze!
去你的  汉克！
Freakin' crap, Hank!
这难道不是超级好的事吗？就咱们几个
Isn't this great? I mean, just us guys
坐在这里  放松一下  打打牌
sitting here, chillin', playin' cards.
你真有一套  猫男
You really know how to sling the zingers, cat guy.
- 我叫阿瓦卡多   - 不  你叫撸瑟
- The name's Avocato. - No. The name is loser!
吃我一发！四带一！
Eat it! Four of a kind!
你一点都没注意到那东西  是不是？
You're oblivious to this thing, aren't you?
- 啥东西？   - 那东西
- What? - That.
- 这个？   - 对！就是这个
- This? - Yes! That.
- 月饼？   - 月饼是啥？
- Mooncake? - What's a Mooncake?
- 是这个！   - 那个？
- This! - That?
- 是的  那个   - 别告诉我你还给E-351起了名字
- Yes, that. - Please tell me you didn't name E-351.
- E-3559又是啥？   - 是那个
- What's an E-3559? - That.
- 这个？   - 喵的就是那个！
- This? - Yes, freakin' that!
那我可能真的起了个名字
I suppose I did.
你不知道那个是什么吧？
You don't know what that is, do you?
那可是个行星杀手
That is a planet-killer.
你听到他说什么了吗？
Are you hearing this?
这人居然说月饼是行星杀手！
Freakin' guy thinks Mooncake is a planet-killer!
这都哪跟哪啊... 我的老天哪！
What a freakin' ... oh, man!
- 你给我闭嘴  KVN！智障   - 你觉得这很好玩？
- Shut your face hole, KVN! Crap. - So you think this is funny?
- 我很严肃   - 你很严肃？
- I'm serious. - Are you?
是的  总司令满银河地找它
Yes. The Lord Commander is searching the galaxy for it.
你藏不住的  无论你去哪  他都会找到你
You can't hide. Wherever you go, he'll find you.
我为什么要相信你  胡子先生？
Why should I believe you, Mr. Whiskers?
再叫我一遍这个名字  我就杀了你
Call me that again, and I'll kill you.
嗯嗯  我还冒犯你了  实际上
Mm-hmm. I've insulted you. You see, the truth is,
我从来没和猫人打过交道
I've never socialized with a cat man before.
我邻居有只猫  很喜欢舔自己
My neighbor had a cat. Loved to lick himself.
你不会舔自己吧？不会吧？
You're not gonna do that, right?
不然  我们之间就有问题了  朋友
Otherwise, we're gonna have problems, friend.
我不是猫  我是文特里西人
I'm not a cat, I'm a Ventrexian.
我知道了  我还是个长老派教徒呢
Got it. See, I'm a Presbyterian myself.
但我爱所有人
But I love all people.
- 我从小受到的教育就是这样的   - 我们有麻烦了
- Just how I was raised. - We're in danger.
听着  我们都有麻烦了！
Listen, all of us are in danger!
月饼  看看盖瑞圆圆的眼珠
Mooncake, look into Gary's gelatinous marbles.
只要我还有一口气
As long as I draw breath and you provide me
只要你还能给我带来无尽的冒险
with copious amounts of adventure,
我就会一直陪着你  我们是一个团队
I will be there for you. We're a team now.
我会让你当我的好朋友
And I'll let you be my sidekick and such
我也会成为你的好朋友
with a super side order of what-not.
说得好
Well said.
一块饼干... 这是给我的？！
A cookie ... for me?!
是的  盖瑞  拿一块吧
Yes, Gary. Take one.
你展现出了一种我之前没在你身上见过的品质
You displayed a quality I hadn't seen in you previously...
勇气  堪称典范的勇气  你配的上拿一块
courage. Exemplary. You earned it.
我能拿饼干  还因为我是舰长大人啊！
And because I am the captain!
饼干收回了
Cookie withdrawn.
悔悟之人必得原谅
The penitent man shall pass.
哦！我拿到了！
Ohh! I got one!
格兰多的手套啊  我拿到了一块饼干！
Sweet Grandor's glove, I got a mother-loving cookie!
这是一块饼干  奎恩
This is a cookie, Quinn.
HUE说这是我自己挣来的  因为我做了大事  奎恩
HUE said I earned it because I did things, Quinn.
危险的事
Dangerous things.
值得赢得饼干的事
Cookie-earning things.
现在  我要吃掉我光荣的成果了
Now to eat the fruits of my greatness.
- 是我的了！   - 啥？不要！
- Mine! - What? No!
KVN！哦  KVN！
KVN! Oh, KVN!
盖瑞？盖瑞？盖瑞？！
Gary? Gary? Gary?!
盖瑞？盖瑞  盖瑞！
Gary? Gary. Gary!
盖瑞  你在睡吗？
Gary, are you sleeping?
Wah-pa!
哦  好的好的  我们... 我们很好  别理我
Oh, okay. We... we're good. Don't mind me.
我... 我这就往这边走
I'm ... I'm just floating this way.
这边是我想走的路
This is the way I like to go.
拜拜！这是我的想法  这是我的道路
Bye! This was my plan. That's my path.
所有棋子都就位了
All the pieces are in place.
让我陪你玩一会吧
Let's play a little.
Sync & Correction by f1nc0 from Addic7ed.com